JEFFREY GUMBS

WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a dedicated web developer with a focus on crafting immersive online experiences. I excel in front-end and back-end development, combining creativity with technical expertise to bring innovative websites and web applications to life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Administrative Asssitant

Classic Landscapes Limited | Jul 2014 - Jan 2023

- Conduct day-to-day IT tasks and functionality of employee stationery.
- Implement upgrades to the company network and reduce the cost.
- Assure that the company network is running efficiently for both employees and clients.
- Maintain the company Web site with other skills

Jr IT Assistant

Harbour Group of Company | Nov 2010 - Oct 2013

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Maintain and clean the server room
- Computer and Hardware repair for all departments in the company.
- · Set up equipment in the board room for meetings
- · Work with others on projects to ensure their success

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

New England Institute Technology

Programmer | Sep 2006 - Jun 2007

- Studied Softeware Engernier
- Desktop App Development



CONTACT ME AT



780-665-5044



jeffreygumbs@gmail.com



www.jeffreygumbs.io



https://github.com/jeffreygumbs



576 Lakewood Road North NW, Edmonton AB

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Networking
- Cyber Security
- Data Management and Analystic
- Cloud Computing
- Cloud Management
- App Development and Management

CERTIFICATE

- Junior to Senior web developer 2022
- Full Stack Developer 2019
- E.C. Council Ethical Hacker 2012